(Penny:)Yeah, that'll slow it down.
[BOTH PANTING]
(Steph:)I'm sorry, I totally interrupted you.
What were you saying?
(Sheldon:)Oh.
(Leonard:)Right, yeah. Um...
(Leonard:)So, Stephanie, here's the thing.
(Leonard:)- I really like you...
- Oh, God, here comes the speech.
(Leonard:)What speech?
(Steph:)I really like you but maybe we should spend
a little less time together...
...because I need my space,
but I'll call you on Tuesday.
(Steph:)And then you never call me, so I call you,
but you don't call me back.
(Steph:)And then when I run into you
at the coffee shop...
...you pretend you have problems
with voice mail...
(Steph:)...and I know that you're lying
but I pretend like I don't care...
(Steph:)...even though I'm dying inside.